Look over here.
JoJo!
Tell me you're seeing this!
Just keep your guard up, Koichi,
and don't get any closer to it.
Hey, didn't you hear me?
I said look over here.
Is that his stand? JoJo!
Look at the coat rack!
The killer is here, and he's
trying to take the jacket!
Ah, good grief.
This would be when he
comes to get his suit.
Our evidence!
Wait!
We can't go blindly after it.
What is his power?
Watch out, it's gonna blow!
I don't know.
What the?
The owner blew up!
The killer has a bomb stand!
It all makes sense now.
This is how he got Shigechi! Oh, God.
That's why we couldn't
find his body anywhere.
He's getting away!
Calm down, Koichi. Let him go. Huh?
What do you mean, let him go?
You can't be serious!
If we go after him now,
we might actually have a shot at catching
the bastard who murdered
Reimi and Shigechi!
We need to observe the situation
before making our move.
Be patient, Koichi.
Do you even hear yourself?
Not gonna lie.
Getting a look at that name
tag would have been a big help.
But given that jacket's size, we
know he's about 175 centimeters tall.
What's more, he's an
unmarried office worker.
If he were married, he wouldn't need
to come here to get a button fixed.
He's between the ages of 25 and 35.
And from the look of the
jacket, he's pretty damn rich.
The jacket's unique fabric and styling
tell us he tends to wear designer clothing,
even without a good look at him.
This info alone just narrowed
our target down big time.
You know, that does make sense.
Wait a second, we can't just
stay here sitting on our hands!
The guy is a cold-blooded killer!
I want to chase him as much as
you do, but we have to stay put.
The bomb stand is somewhere over there.
It's still here?
Where do you see it?
I haven't seen it yet,
but I know it's here.
Let's make our way out of the door.
Slowly.
Wait, you just know?
But how is that possible?
There's no way you could know its
location if you haven't seen it.
He's not the kind of killer to bomb and
run after only offing that shop owner.
Just think about it.
If he was, his killing spree
would have ended a long time ago.
He doesn't like to leave behind evidence.
Which means he intends to take us out too.
I understand that, but don't you think
you're being a teensy bit overcautious?
If you're wrong about this
and his stand isn't here,
our murderer and evidence
could be long gone by now!
Listen, Koichi.
Observing involves far more
than just looking around.
It means scrutinizing everything.
You don't simply listen, you concentrate.
Otherwise, we'll die in this room.
I don't like what he was implying.
My reverb is more than strong
enough to keep us safe.
It's matured a lot since it emerged.
Maybe Mr.
Jotaro just doesn't take me seriously.
Well, if you asked me, that
dumb bomb stand is long gone.
I mean, we'd have to be total
numb nuts not to see it.
Over here!
He was right!
It was here all along!
It'll explode if I keep touching it!
Star Platinum!
Damn, it's tough.
I knocked it to shit, and the
thing's still in one piece.
I think it's gonna blow!
Star Platinum, bring forth the world!
I'd like to end this
before things get ugly,
so I'm disposing of
you right here and now.
It's gone.
You must have stopped
time and finished it off.
Bet you didn't see that one
coming, did you, murderer?
Anyone who dares pursue
Yoshikage Kira must be destroyed.
I'll blow them to little pieces.
They think they've won, but once Deadly
Queen's heart attack finds its prey,
it won't rest until its target is dead.
There's no way!
Not even Star Platinum had
enough power to destroy it,
which means it's practically invincible!
Damn it!
Stay behind me, Koichi.
It hasn't taken any damage!
Nothing we do seems to
face this thing whatsoever!
I can see that. Get back.
You've been hitting it so
hard you're starting to bleed,
but it still doesn't have
a single scratch on it.
For the last time, get back, Koichi.
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
It'll explode and take
us along for the ride.
You have to get rid of it.
Look over here!
Good freaking grief.
This is a first for me.
That Stan's resilience is insane.
The way this is going, my confidence
will break before it does.
What now, Mr. Jotaro?
We're not going to be able
to hold out for much longer.
You're still too close for comfort.
I'm going to destroy this
alarm clock from hell.
I beg you, you have to listen to me.
When a stand's controlled from a distance,
it only wields a fraction
of its full power.
Look at the way it charges and
the intensity of its explosions.
Its owner has to be nearby
fueling it with energy.
There's no other explanation.
At most 15.
No, based on what we've seen,
the killer's 10 meters away.
And?
What do you mean, and?
It's 10 meters and Reverb
has a range of 50 meters.
I can find that prick.
Don't you move.
Koichi, just leave it be.
You have one job, and it's to focus
on protecting yourself with Reverb.
Nothing else matters now.
You're letting him get away?
The guy's long gone, Koichi.
That means we're dealing
with a long-range stand.
Trust me, I've seen enough of these
to know what I'm talking about.
Over here!
Its movements are too simple
for a short-range stand.
He's seen enough of them to know?
Is he off his rocker?
We're going up against an incredibly
powerful long-range stand.
The user has to be close by.
I knew Mr.
Jotaro didn't take me seriously.
But I'll show him how much I've matured.
I'll find the killer and
finish him off by myself.
Ten meter range.
There, I found him.
And he has the jacket with him.
What's going on?
He's too far away.
That's much farther than 50 meters.
He's still going.
Now he's outside Reverb's range.
Does that mean the killer
really has the ability
to control such a
powerful stand from afar?
Impossible.
Over here! What?
Oh no, it's aiming at me!
Now I get it.
For some reason, the bomb stand is drawn
to whichever object it senses is hottest.
That would explain the range
and why it's still so powerful.
Use Reverb to protect yourself.
Stopping time is useless at that distance.
Oh crap, I can't.
I sent Reverb 50 meters away
to track down the killer.
Sorry, I didn't listen.
Good freaking grief, kid.
Star Platinum, once more the world!
It attacked the shop owner first
because of the hot liquid in his cup.
Compared to that, our
body heat didn't register.
But in Koichi's case, his frustration
increased his temperature.
If it detects something hotter,
then it moves on to that.
Enough, time resume.
I was right.
Since it's drawn to the highest
temperature it can detect,
it's making a beeline for me.
What is he planning? All right.
If body temperature is all
it takes to trigger this,
then fire should be more than enough.
This power!
Mr. Chotaro!
Mr.
Chotaro!
How could I let this happen? Mr.
Chotaro, this is all my fault!
All because I went after that bastard!
This wouldn't have happened if he hadn't
had to stop time and
save me with that fire!
That was not the sensation
of human flesh exploding.
Over here.
Ah! Ah!
It's gonna kill us!
It's just too powerful!
It's like Mr.
Jotaro was saying.
If it detects a temperature hotter than
body heat, it goes after that first.
Over here!
Now's our chance to make a break for it.
I need to find a way to call Josuke.
He'll be able to fix Mr. Jotaro.
I just need to find a phone!
Oh, of course!
It's the kitchen!
Lots of ways to start a fire in here!
I'll buy some time, and then
we'll escape through that door.
A phone!
Wait!
You have got to be kidding me!
This isn't a gas stove!
Why the hell does this house
have to have an electric one?
I bet it's gonna take forever to get hot.
Aw, come on! The oven, too?
What do I do now?
I bet that kettle has hot water in it!
Try and fight me now!
Ah! It's empty!
Get over here!
Calm down.
It's like Mr. Jotaro said.
I need to carefully observe. Focus.
This thing has a weakness.
I never noticed it until now.
You're really starting to piss me off.
You're nothing but a repulsive murderer,
a stain on the fabric of humanity.
Why should a Dark like
you have the satisfaction
of watching me flee and beg for mercy?
Shouldn't the roles be reversed?
I already know that I can get out of
this mess alive, so for the life of me,
I can't figure out why I'm just standing
here like a wimpy little bitch baby?
with a bad case of the shits.
I've had this all wrong
from the beginning!
The one who should be
running away is you, dick!
This ends once and for all!
You're unrelenting in your
pursuit of thermal energy,
but that's also your shortcoming!
Your inability to stuff
will be your undoing!
You're gonna pay for your crimes, so
consider this the first installment!
It's been three minutes
since I made my escape.
I don't know what's transpired at
the shoe store in the meantime,
but no matter how strong my
opponent There's one thing.
I'm certain of heart attack is the
ultimate stand and has no weaknesses
It'll find and destroy
any target without fail.
Okay, with that thing out of the way,
all that's left is to call Josuke!
He should have made it
home from school by now.
At least that pest is
distracted for the time being.
I don't think it'll fool it forever,
but the sizzle should keep it busy
long enough to make a phone call.
Lucky for me,
the little jackass is as gullible as
a donkey chasing a hanging carrot.
And that's your stance fatal flaw.
Gashkata residents.
Josuke, it's Koichi, I need help!
Jotaro's hurt, I don't
think he's gonna make it!
It's kinda my fault, but
still, get here fast!
Mm-hmm.
You want to run that by me again?
What the hell is going on?
Just focus on getting here.
We found the killer.
We were following a hunch at first,
but long story short, I'm
holding his stand captive.
What do you mean, holding it captive?
Are you there?
It's hard to hear.
Where are you right now?
Wait, that's weird.
Ah, it's hot.
I turned this thing off a while ago,
so why in the world is it
just starting to heat up now?
What is with this heap of junk?
I don't know how anybody
cooks a damn thing with it!
Come in, Koichi!
Tell me where you are so I can find you!
Over here!
Oh, shit!
It's totally ignoring Reverb's writing!
Koichi, where are you?
Hurry up and tell me, you idiot!
We're at Mukadeya Shoes!
Get over here now!
Damn it!
Reverb's tail is still attached to it!
That hurt, not only did it blow up,
the damage got transferred to me.
That was not the sensation
of human flesh exploding.
Over here.
Just what I didn't need.
It's getting ready to attack, but
I can't use Reverb's tail anymore.
What's my next move?
How can I fight back?
Let's go, River, act two!
Where'd you go?
River, act two!
Act two!
Why aren't you showing yourself?
What's the matter?
Oh, no!
Act two must have been
killed in the explosion!
He's just the husk of his former self!
No, don't freak out just yet.
If it died in that blast,
then I should have been killed
too, but that didn't happen.
Right, it's coming back to me.
This isn't the first time Reberb
has looked like a lifeless shell.
Does that mean...
Could it be?
Reverb, act three!
Um, if that's you, your new
form looks a lot different.
Act three, awaiting orders.
Oh, yeah, I was right. I told Mr.
Jotaro my powers had matured.
You are the best stand ever,
act three, you know that?
I'm still awaiting your orders. Well,
I'm not all that familiar with
your new capabilities so for
now I guess just protect us
from harm get to it act three
Um, I mean, please keep
us safe back three sir.
You can do that right command acquired
Ahhhh!
This is insane!
Whoa!
I thought it was fast
before, but this is crazy!
Compared to this kind of speed, Acts 1
and 2 were as slow as geriatric turtles!
Activating Reverb Act 3
Special Ability 3 Freeze!
What the?
Hey, what the heck happened out there,
Act 3? Too strong. There's no hope.
Then we have to find some!
We're doing battle with an adversary
that possesses Herculean strength.
It's time for us to face the music.
We're S-H-I-T out of luck.
Have you lost it?
I commanded you to protect us from harm,
so get your butt in gear
and start protecting!
The act of protecting
you has been completed.
Exactly as you ordered.
Over here!
It's been completed, but
you said we should give up!
You know what, buddy?
I think you're malfunctioning!
You haven't made the
slightest bit of progress!
Over here!
What the hell?
This skirmish is taking far too long.
What is keeping Heart Attack?
It normally makes the kill by now.
What the hell is happening?
My left hand feels as
heavy as a cement block.
This was the hand that I
released heart attack with.
And now...
Evening, sir.
I hope everything's alright.
Can I help at all? No, thanks.
Bring me the bill.
And please allow me to pay for the cup.
There's something that needs
my attention, so hop to it.
This indentation!
Why is my left hand so heavy?
Sir, are you okay?
What the hell is this?
My left hand weighs a ton.
It feels like there's a massive
weight pressing against it.
What is happening over there?
Do you need some assistance, sir?
No, everything's just fine.
Really, let go.
This weight!
Good heavens, sir.
Was it something I said?
It's been driven so far into the
pavement, it's barely moving.
Wow, Act Three, what's this new ability?
It's amazing!
Three frees.
Three and free.
It works because they rhyme.
Yeah, that's nice, but it
doesn't answer my question.
I want to know why the
bomb stand's barely moving.
Don't leave me hanging.
Well, I did just tell you
they rhyme, Master Koichi.
Need I say any more?
I have no idea how those
mentalsome twits did it,
but somehow they were able
to weigh down heart attack.
Shit, how did it come to this?
I have to go back to that shop
and fetch heart attack myself
Anytime I need to see a
face, it has closed my eyes.
And I am taking two bits
with a crystal mind.
A magenta feeling.
Take a shelter in the face of my spine.
Straight like a Chaka cherry cola.
I don't need to try to explain.
I just hold on tight.
And if it happens again,
I'ma move so slightly.
To the arms and the lips and the face.
To the humic and the ball that I need to.
I want to.
Come stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what hit you.
When I get to you.
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you.
Ooh, I gotta find help.
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you.
Ooh, I gotta find help.